# **KOMAL RAOSAHEB SHINDE**

Baner, Pune City • 8698431735 • komal.shindesk07@gmail.com

#### **SUMMARY**

To contribute to the success of an organization by fully utilizing my skills and knowledge in the field of Software Development in a position offering continuous growth. I am Bachelor of computer engineering with 4.9 years of professional experience. Continuously learning and staying updated with the latest trends in Angular development.

### **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

Angular, Java, Java Script, Type Script, HTML, CSS, Git, Postman and Jira

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### Software Developer(Angular), Prakhar Software Solutions Pvt Ltd.

25 Aug 2021 to Present

Client: -Armament Research and Development Establishment (ARDE

Project Name: E Approval for IMMS (Integrated Material Management System)

## Responsibilities:

- Deployment and maintain codes.
- Analyze user requirements and convert requirements to design documents.
- Develop and implement new software programs using Angular.
- Test, maintain and recommend software improvements to ensure strong functionality
- Built client-side interface for projects using Angular Js, Angular 12, Java Script, CSS and HTML.

## Software Developer, Redwing Infotech Pvt Ltd.

27 Mar 2020 - 23 Aug 2021

Project - iDO Management System.

Responsibilities:

- Creating a web based application using MVC architecture in Java adding web pages using Angular Js, Angular 12, HTML, JSP.
- Perform CRUD operation on this application.
- · Adding permission in it.

## RPA Developer, Tata Technologies Pvt Ltd.

26 Mar 2019 - 25 Mar 2020

Project - Distribution of Plex System.

Client - Plex Inc.

Tool - Automation Anywhere

## Responsibilities:

- Analysis of requirement and test case preparation.
- Gather knowledge about tool handling bot using AA query.
- Testing and Defect Management.
- Helping in peers and resolving there query.
- Suggesting Improvement.
- Conducting exploratory testing.
- · Identification of critical scenario.

#### **EDUCATION**

**Bachelor of Engineering in Computer Science** 

2015-2018

JSPM RSCOE Tathwade, Pune

**Diploma in Computer Science** 

2012-2015

Indira Gandhi Polytechnic ,Ahmednagar